http://www.oli.org/privacy-policy

Rail Safety Week
See Tracks? Think Train!
Transit Riders
UtilityVolunteerRequest a Safety PresentationMaterialsLoginSearch siteSubmit search
Privacy Policy
Operation Lifesaver, Inc. Privacy Notice
Effective Date:  November 1, 2019
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for Operation Lifesaver, Inc. and our website, https://oli.org, and our rail safety public awareness campaign website, https://www.seetracksthinktrain.org/. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by these websites, except where stated otherwise.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request. Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about new products or information.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You will receive e-mail communication from Operation Lifesaver, Inc. only if you have requested it, or if you have signed up for a newsletter or made a donation. You can remove your e-mail address from our database at any time by sending an e-mail to general@oli.org or by sending written correspondence to the following address: Website, Operation Lifesaver, Inc., 425 Third Street SW, Suite 915, Washington, D.C. 20024.
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address above:
See what data we have about you, if any
Change/correct any data we have about you
Have us delete any data we have about you
Express any concern you have about our use of your data
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.
As a condition of accessing this website, you, the user, agree not to infect it with a computer virus, Trojan Horse, or other malicious software.
Cookies
We use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance their experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.
Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (e.g., advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.
Links
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
Surveys & Contests
From time to time our site may request information via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you may choose whether to participate. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.
Policy Changes
From time to time, this privacy policy may be updated to describe new features or services, or changes in privacy practices. The latest version will always appear on our website.
Other Provisions
Your personal data is processed in the United States, where privacy laws may be less stringent than the laws in your country. By submitting your personal data to us, you agree to the transfer, storage, and processing of your personal data in the United States. Numerous other provisions and/or practices may be required as a result of laws, international treaties, or industry practices. It is up to you to determine what additional practices must be followed and/or what additional disclosures are required.
Footer menu
News
Materials
Contact
Privacy Policy
Connect with us on Social MediaSocial media linksFacebookLinkedInInstagramPinterestTwitterYouTube
Copyright 2020 Operation Lifesaver, Inc.
